samsbox.com 2013-11-27

# SamsBox / Privacy Policy

* * *

#### PRIVACY POLICY

Samsbox.COM

Last Updated: _January 30th, 2013_

This Privacy policy covers your rights, and our use of your Data and other information we collect and use. For more details on security policies or terms, please see the other pages on the Website. 

#### Highlights

  * We use a highly secure form of Private Key Encryption, which means that your data is encrypted on your own computer before it is transmitted to us. This means that nobody, not even our employees or law enforcement, can read your data stored on our servers. 
  * Your data is encrypted multiple times for added layers of security: When you enter your password (AES 128 or 256 bit), when it is transmitted to us (SSL connection), and when it is stored in our servers (Randomized Salting). 
  * If you lose your Password, we cannot recover your data
  * We never sell or share your personal information with anyone, except to comply with the law or protect our rights. 
  * We don't store your passwords or encryption keys on our servers to keep your data truly private
  * Login & Signup through our Linkedin application is required to fully use all the features of our Service; this requires you to have a valid Linkedin user account, which is subject to its own privacy policy and terms. 
  * If you are under the age of 13, you may not use our Service. 

This Privacy Policy provides our policies and procedures for collecting, using, and disclosing your information. Users can access the Samsbox service (the “Service”) through our website www.Samsbox.com, applications on Devices, through APIs, and through third-parties. A “Device” is any computer used to access the Samsbox Service, including without limitation a desktop, laptop, mobile phone, tablet, or other consumer electronic device. This Privacy Policy governs your access of the Samsbox Service, regardless of how you access it, and by using our Services you consent to the collection, transfer, processing, storage, disclosure and other uses described in this Privacy Policy. All of the different forms of data, content, and information described below are collectively referred to as “information.”

#### INFORMATION WE COLLECT

We may collect the following information from you when you use our Service:

**Encrypted Data & Files:** This is information you entered into the "Secure" text editor page of our Service, which may include passwords to other services, personal or financial info etc. This also includes any files you upload into the File Vault. This information is encrypted on your machine, and again during transmission, before it is received by us for storage. We cannot identify, open, or access this information, other than associating it with your account. You have full rights of ownership over this information and can edit or delete it at any time. 

**IP Address, Browser Information & other MetaData:** This is used to build an Internet connection with your computer so we can appropriately transfer information from and to your computer, and to customize content for your browser or computer type. 

**Cookies:** These are used for session-management, to log you into your account, and for security management. We do not run advertisements or offer third-parties access to your personal or cookie information at any time for marketing or solicitation. Cookies may be used in aggregate form by us to view trends and usage data by analytics software such as Google analytics. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your Device. We may use “persistent cookies” to save your registration ID and login password for future logins to the Service. We may use “session ID cookies” to enable certain features of the Service, to better understand how you interact with the Service and to monitor aggregate usage and web traffic routing on the Service. You can instruct your browser, by changing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all aspects of the Service.

**LinkedIn Application UserID:** This is a non-personally-identifiable token passed to us by Linkedin when you authorize our application on their platform. We do not get access at any time to your Linkedin credentials, password or other sensitive information. You may choose not to authorize our application, however, you may not be able to use all aspects of the Service. 

**Email address, Name, Password:** When you register an account with us, you provide certain information including email, name, password and other personal info. You may also ask us to import your contacts by giving us access to your third party services (for example, your email account or LinkedIn) or to use your social networking information if you give us access to your account on social network connection services. When you invite others to join Samsbox by using our referral page, we send them a one-time email for that referral. You may also provide us with your contacts’ email addresses when sharing folders or files with them. We may also receive Personal Information (for example, your email address) through other users, for example if they have tried to share something with you or tried to refer Samsbox to you.

Mobile phone number (optional)

Credit Card or other payment information (optional)

#### PROTECTION OF CERTAIN PERSONALLY-IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION

Samsbox discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Samsbox' behalf or to provide services available at Samsbox' websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Samsbox' websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Samsbox will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Samsbox discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when Samsbox believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Samsbox, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an Samsbox website and have supplied your email address, Samsbox may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what's going on with Samsbox and our products. We expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Samsbox takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

#### INFORMATION SHARING & DISCLOSURE

Your Use. We will display your Personal Information in your profile page and elsewhere on the Service according to the preferences you set in your account. Any information you choose to provide will remain private to your account and will not be shared with other users. You can review and revise your profile information at any time. We do not sell your personal information to third parties. 

Service Providers, Business Partners and Others. We may use certain trusted third party companies and individuals to help us provide, analyze, and improve the Service (including but not limited to data storage, maintenance services, database management, web analytics, payment processing, and improvement of the Service’s features). These third parties may have access to your information only for purposes of performing these tasks on our behalf and under obligations similar to those in this Privacy Policy. As of the date this policy went into effect, we use Amazon’s S3 storage service to store some of your information (for example, your Encrypted Files). You can find more information on Amazon's data security from the S3 site. Credit card payments for example are processed by our PCI-compliant payment processor Stripe and Paypal, and they will have access to your payment information if you choose to enter it. 

Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement Requests; Protection of Samsbox's Rights. We may disclose to parties outside Samsbox files stored in your Samsbox and information about you that we collect when we have a good faith belief that disclosure is reasonably necessary to (a) comply with a law, regulation or compulsory legal request; (b) protect the safety of any person from death or serious bodily injury; (c) prevent fraud or abuse of Samsbox or its users; or (d) to protect Samsbox’s property rights. If we provide your Samsbox files to a law enforcement agency as set forth above, your files will still remain encrypted and secure since we do not have access to the encryption keys (your "Password") used to encrypt your data. 

Business Transfers. If we are involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of our assets, your information may be transferred as part of that transaction, but we will notify you (for example, via email and/or a prominent notice on our website) of any change in control or use of your Personal Information or Files, or if either become subject to a different Privacy Policy. We will also notify you of choices you may have regarding the information.

Non-private or Non-Personal Information. We may disclose your non-private, aggregated, or otherwise non-personal information, such as usage statistics of our Service.

#### CHANGING OR DELETING YOUR INFORMATION

If you are a registered user, you may review, update, correct or delete the Personal Information and Encrypted Data/Files provided in your registration or account profile by changing your “account settings.” If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may update or delete it by making the change on your account settings. In some cases we may retain copies of your information if required by law. For questions about your Personal Information on our Service, please contact us. We will respond to your inquiry within 3 business days. 

#### DATA RETENTION

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services, you may delete your account here. We may retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. Consistent with these requirements, we will try to delete your information quickly upon request. Please note, however, that there might be latency in deleting information from our servers and backed-up versions might exist after deletion. 

#### SECURITY

The security of your information is very important to us. For a comprehensive overview of what we do to protect your information, please visit our Security Overview page. We take considerable precautions to protect our servers and your information, including but not limited to multiple encryption/decryption cycles, firewalls, backups, and private encryption keys. Please keep in mind however that no method of electronic transmission or storage is 100% secure (although we come pretty close). Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security under any and all conditions. 

#### CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY

This Privacy Policy may change from time to time. If we make a change to this privacy policy that we believe materially reduces your rights, we will provide you with notice (for example, by email). And we may provide notice of changes in other circumstances as well. By continuing to use the Service after those changes become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy.
